chris@tackphoto.com http://christack.com

Chris Tack

Profile

With over 10 years experience in photography, video & design, I would love to pivot my career into a software developer role to utilize my rapid & continually growing skillset.

Projects

SeattleTransit - Mobile-first web app created using One Bus Away API. Users can query a bus stop near their current location & view a list of incoming busses for a specific stop. Built with Node.js, EJS, JS, HTML5

Tools Everywhere - Tool library app where users can log in and add tools they own to the sharing library. Built with Django, HTML5, CSS, Materialize

Simon Game - A take on the game Simon. Built with vanilla JS, HTML5 and CSS. The game displays a pattern that players then repeat back as the sequence increases by one each round

Technical Skills

Javascript CSS HTML5 NodeJS Express React Django Materialize Bootstrap Python Heroku Adobe CC QA Testing

Owner – Tack Photography – 2007-present

Experience

- Consulted with key project stakeholders with the City of Kenmore to build a photo asset library for use in marketing materials, ads & social media
- Managed the execution and creation of a series of 12 videos for the Snohomish Conservation District (scripting, video & sound production, editing and delivery)

Photographer / Videographer - zulily Inc. - 2013-present

- Consulted with internal marketing team to produce and edit video and stills for use on TV, online ads, social media and live broadcast (Facebook Live & live events)
- Establish appropriate lighting to meet shot composition needs.
- Maintained zulily brand consistency alongside featured brands.
- Partnered with stylist to develop ideas for editorial and lifestyle imagery.
- Advised senior management regarding equipment purchases to maximize available budget
- Deliver photographers feedback to elevate standards and consistency

Lead Creative, Inventory Control, Trainer - Apple Inc. - 2005-2012

- Facilitated new employee training and existing employee developmental training
- Delivered coaching and feedback to peers & managers to create team strength and unity
- Headed & mentored team of 30+ to deliver over 10,000 training sessions annually
- Simplified complex technology concepts to ensure customer & employee understanding

Education

General Assembly, Seattle WA – Web Developer Immersive – 2018

Kendall College of Art & Design, Grand Rapids MI – BFA: Photography & Graphic Design – 2007

Activities

Race Crew Volunteer / Photographer/Videographer - SkiHawks Racing Team, 2012 - Present Volunteer - Outdoors For All Foundation, 2012 - Present Special Olympics Michigan: Coach 2000-2006, Volunteer 1994 - 1999 & 2012 - Present